<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:background="@drawable/backgroundmain">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/header"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintRight_toRightOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintLeft_toLeftOf="parent"
        android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
        android:layout_marginHorizontal="20dp"
        android:text="Terms of Service"
        android:textSize="40dp"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:fontFamily="@font/raleway_bold"
        />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/terms_of_service_box"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="550dp"
        app:layout_constraintRight_toRightOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintLeft_toLeftOf="parent"
        android:layout_marginHorizontal="35dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/header"
        android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
        android:background="@drawable/background_right_orange"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        android:textSize="13dp"
        android:textAlignment="textStart"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:paddingHorizontal="13dp"
        android:paddingVertical="25dp"
        android:text="Last Updated: March 29th, 2020\n\nThank you for using Rentathon!\n\nThese Terms constitute a legally binding agreement (‘Agreement’) between you and Rentathon (as defined below) governing your access to and use of the Rentathon app, including any subdomains thereof, and any other websites through which Rentathon makes its services available. The Site and Application together are hereinafter collectively referred to as the ‘Rentathon Platform’. Our Lost Product Guarantee and other Policies applicable to your use of the Rentathon Platform are incorporated by reference into this Agreement.\n\n1.Scope of Rentathon Services\n\n1.1: Rentathon is an online platform that enables users to loan out their items (such Users, the ‘Renters’) to other Users who desire to borrow the Renters' items (such Users, the ‘Rentees’) in exchange for payment of fees to the applicable Renter and Rentathon in the form of a commission. Each such lending transaction between Renters and Rentees shall, for the purposes of these Terms, be referred to as a ‘Renting transaction’ and each item that is the subject of a Lending Transaction shall for the purposes of these Terms, be referred to as an ‘Item’.\n\n2.Eligibility, Using the Rentathon Platform, Member Verification\n\n2.1: This is a contract between you and Rentathon. You must read and agree to these Terms before using the Rentathon Platform. If you do not agree, you may not use the Rentathon Platform. You may use the Rentathon Platform only if you can form a binding contract with Rentathon, and only in compliance with these Terms and all applicable local, state, national, and international laws, rules and regulations. Any use or access to the Rentathon Platform by anyone under fifteen (15) years of age is strictly prohibited and in violation of these Terms. The Rentathon Platform is not available to any Users previously removed from the Rentathon Platform by Rentathon. Rentathon reserves the right to approve or reject any Users from joining or continuing to use the Rentathon Platform, except as prohibited by applicable law.\n\n2.2: User verification on the Internet is difficult and we do not assume any responsibility for the confirmation of any Member’s identity. However, for transparency and fraud prevention purposes, and as permitted by applicable laws, we may, but have no obligation to (i) ask Members to provide a form of government identification or other information or undertake additional checks designed to help verify the identities or backgrounds of Members, (ii) screen Members against third party databases or other sources and request reports from service providers, and (iii) where we have sufficient information to identify a Member, obtain reports from public records of criminal convictions or sex offender registrations or an equivalent version of background or registered sex offender checks in your local jurisdiction.\n\n2.3: Some areas of the Rentathon Platform implement Google Maps/Earth mapping services, including Google Maps API(s). Your use of Google Maps/Earth is subject to the Google Maps/Google Earth Additional Terms of Service.\n\n3.Modification of these Terms\n\n3.1: Rentathon reserves the right to modify these terms at any time. If we make changes to these Terms, we will post a revised version on the Rentathon Platform and update the ‘Last Updated’ field at the top of this document. We will also provide you an email notice of these new Terms. We will inform you about your right to terminate the Agreement in the notification email. Continued use of the Rentathon Platform will constitute acceptance of the revised Terms.\n\n4.Account Registration\n\n4.1: You must register an account (‘Rentathon Account’) to access and use certain features of the Rentathon Platform, such as renting out an item or renting an item.\n\n4.2: You can register a  Rentathon Account using an email address and creating a password, or through your account with certain third-party social networking services, such as Facebook or Google (‘SNS Account’).\n\n4.3: You must provide accurate, current and complete information during the registration process and keep your Rentathon Account and public Rentathon Account profile page information up-to-date at all times.\n\n4.4: You may not register more than one (1) Rentathon Account unless Rentathon authorizes you to do so. You may not assign or otherwise transfer your Rentathon Account to another party.\n\n4.5: You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your Rentathon Account credentials and may not disclose your credentials to any third party. You must immediately notify Rentathon if you know or have any reason to suspect that your credentials have been lost, stolen, misappropriated, or otherwise compromised or in case of any actual or suspected unauthorized use of your Rentathon Account. You are liable for any and all activities conducted through your Rentathon Account, unless such activities are not authorized by you and you are not otherwise negligent (such as failing to report the unauthorized use or loss of your credentials).\n\n5.User Content\n\n5.1: Any and all photographs, articles, images, graphics, videos, sounds, music, audio recordings, text, files, profiles, communications, comments, feedback, suggestions, ideas, concepts, questions, data or other content that you: (i) submit or post on or through the Rentathon Platform, social media accounts or through tools or applications we provide for posting or sharing such content with us; or (ii) have posted or uploaded to your social media accounts which are tagged with any Rentathon promoted hashtag (collectively ‘User Content’), shall be deemed nonconfidential and nonproprietary. You understand that certain portions of the Rentathon platform may allow other Users to view, edit, share, and/or otherwise interact with your User Content. By providing or sharing User Content through the Rentathon Platform, you agree to allow others to view, edit, share, and/or interact with your User Content in accordance with your settings and these Terms.\n\n5.2: WE CLAIM NO OWNERSHIP RIGHTS OVER THE USER CONTENT CREATED BY YOU. THE USER CONTENT REMAINS YOURS. However, by submitting or posting any User Content, you hereby expressly grant to Rentathon and its affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, worldwide license to copy, publish, translate, modify, reformat, distribute, reproduce, sell, display, transmit, publish, broadcast, host, archive, store, use or otherwise exploit all or any portion of the User Content, as well as your name, persona and likeness included in any User Content and your social media account handle, username, real name, profile picture and/or any other information associated with the User Content, in any commercial or noncommercial manner.\n\n5.3: Rentathon does not guarantee the truthfulness, accuracy or reliability of any User Content or endorse any opinions expressed by you or anyone else. By submitting or posting the User Content you fully and unconditionally release and forever discharge Rentathon and its officers, directors, employees and agents from any and all claims, demands and damages (actual or consequential, direct or indirect), whether now known or unknown, of every kind.\n\n5.4: Rentathon has the absolute right to remove/delete user content without any notice if the content is objectionable. You consent to such removal and waive any claim against Rentathon for such a removal or deletion.\n\n5.5: The Rentathon Platform may contain links to third-party materials that are not owned or controlled by Rentathon. Rentathon does not endorse or assume any responsibility for any such third-party sites, information, materials, products, or services. If you access a third-party website or service from the Rentathon Platform or share your User Content on or through any third-party website or service, you do so at your own risk, and you understand that these Terms do not apply to your use of such sites. You expressly relieve Rentathon from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website, service, or content, including without limitation User Content submitted by other Users.\n\n6.Terms for Renters\n\n6.1: You may accept or reject any request from a Rentee to enter into a Renting Transaction at your sole discretion. Once you accept a request to enter into a Renting Transaction, a legally binding agreement is formed between you and the Rentee. Once you enter into a Renting Transaction with a Rentee, you agree to be responsive to the Rentee and to communicate with them to coordinate the delivery and return of the Item. If you, as a Renter, cancel a Lending Transaction after you accept the Rentee’s request within 24 hours of the suggested rent, you shall be liable to pay, and you authorize Rentathon to charge your payment method for, a cancellation charge of one day of the Loan Fee (as defined below) and Rentathon may, at its sole discretion, credit the applicable Rentee’s account for a portion of your cancellation charge.\n\n6.2: When listing an Item for Rentees to rent through the Rentathon Platform (such items, the ‘Items’), Renters must: (i) provide complete and accurate information and descriptions about the Items; (ii) disclose any deficiencies, restrictions, and requirements that apply; and (iii) provide any other pertinent information requested by Rentathon. Images used in the Renters' Item listings must accurately reflect the quality and condition of your Items. Rentathon reserves the right to require that Item listings and descriptions have a minimum number of images  of a certain format, size and resolution. These images will be used to determine the quality of your product in the case of a dispute with the Rentee.\n\n6.3: You are solely responsible for setting a price for the Rentee to rent your Items (‘Loan Fee’). Once a Rentee requests to borrow your Items, you may not request that the Rentee pays a higher price than in the request, nor may you do any subsequent verification of the Rentee. Unless otherwise agreed by the parties in writing, Rentathon shall remit payment to you of the Loan Fee due to you, less the Rentathon Commission (as defined below), no later than twenty-four (24) hours after scheduled start of Rentee's Item rental. Payment shall be in the form of electronic payment, or as subsequently updated as permitted by the Rentathon Platform. Rentathon reserves the right to withhold payment or charge back to your account any amounts otherwise due to us under these Terms or amounts due to any breach of these Terms by you, pending Rentathon's reasonable investigation of such breach. Rentathon also reserves the right to withhold payment or charge back to your account any amounts subject to dispute, such as in the case of credit card charge backs, pending successful resolution of the dispute.\n\n6.4: You will not list or rent the following Items on the Rentathon Platform: (i) alcohol, tobacco, and drugs; (ii) illegal items, items promoting illegal activity; (iii) pornography and mature content; (iv) items that violate the Intellectual Property Rights or other proprietary rights of any third party; (v) people, animals and animal products; and/or (vi) any Items that are not clean or in good condition. Rentathon reserves the right to change this list of prohibited Items at any time and for any or no reason and to remove any Items listed on the Rentathon Platform, whether or not they are included on this list of prohibited Items.\n\n6.5: As part of the Rentathon Platform, Rentathon will allow Renters to be compensated for any Items that are lost, stolen or damaged by filing a claim with Rentathon.\n\n6.6: When you lend an Item to a Rentee as part of a Lending Transaction, you acknowledge and agree that you are entering into a transaction with the applicable Rentee – not Rentathon. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THERE ARE RISKS INHERENT TO LENDING YOUR ITEMS TO RENTEES IN CONNECTION WITH A LENDING TRANSACTION – INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OR DESTRUCTION OF YOUR ITEMS AND THAT YOU ASSUME ALL RISK IN CONNECTION WITH LENDING YOUR ITEMS THROUGH THE RENTATHON PLATFORM. WITHOUT LIMITING ANY OTHER PROVISION IN THESE TERMS AND TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE AND RELEASE RENTATHON FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, CLAIMS, CAUSES OF ACTION, OR DAMAGES ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE RENTATHON PLATFORM AS A RENTER.\n\n7.Terms for Rentees\n\n7.1: You may borrow an Item through the Rentathon Platform by submitting a request to the Renter through the Rentathon Platform. You may withdraw your request to borrow an Item without any charge or liability by notifying Rentathon, provided such withdrawal is effected prior to Renter’s acceptance of the request. This process is subject to meeting any and all additional requirements set by Rentathon and/or the Renter.\n\n7.2:  You agree to return the Items no later than the time that is indicated in the accepted renting request; provided that, you may request to extend the rental period from the Renter, who may choose to extend the rental period at the Renter's sole discretion. If you retain the Item beyond the agreed upon time or fail to use reasonable efforts to communicate with the Renter during your rental period to coordinate delivery and return of the Item, you no longer have a license to borrow and use the Item and the Renter is entitled to make you return the Items in a manner consistent with applicable law. In addition, you agree to pay for each twenty-four (24) hour period (or any portion thereof) that you retain the Item, an additional fee of up to the original daily Rental Fee to cover the inconvenience suffered by the Renter and Rentathon, plus all applicable taxes, and any legal expenses incurred by the Renter and Rentathon to make you return the Item unless and until such late fees reach the estimated value of the retained Items. You authorize Rentathon and its third-party payment processors to charge your payment method for the fees described in this Section.\n\n7.3: Rentees are responsible for returning the Items to Renters in the condition it was in when they received the Items. Rentees are responsible for their own actions and are also responsible for the actions of any individuals whom you invite to, or otherwise provide access to or use of the Items, excluding the Renters. In the event the Item is damaged, lost, stolen or destroyed, you agree that Rentathon and its third-party payment processors may charge your payment method for up to the fair market value of the applicable Item to compensate for such damage, loss, or destruction of the Item.\n\n7.4: By submitting a request to enter into a Renting Transaction with a Renter, you acknowledge that: (i) you have read and accepted the description of the Item provided by the Renter; (ii) you have the funds available to cover the required payments to cover the Loan Fees and any late charges for any Items retained after the rental period; (iii) you accept responsibility for the Items and agree to pay any late fees and charges in accordance with terms of this Section; and (iv) you agree to use the Items in compliance with any and all applicable laws, rules, and regulations.\n\n7.5: When you borrow an Item from a Renter as part of a Renting Transaction, you acknowledge and agree that you are entering into a transaction with the applicable Renter – not Rentathon. YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE AND RELEASE RENTATHON FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, CLAIMS, CAUSES OF ACTION, OR DAMAGES ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE RENTATHON PLATFORM AS A RENTEE.\n\n8.Interactions and Disputes between Renters and Rentees\n\n8.1: In the event that a Renter and a Rentee are unable to resolve a dispute between them directly, they may ask Rentathon to mediate the dispute. Rentathon may accept or reject such requests to be a mediator at its sole discretion. If Rentathon accepts the request to act as a mediator, it may charge a fee of any amounts that Rentathon determines is payable by the Rentee to compensate the Renter for any loss or damage to the applicable Item. We will charge this amount to the Rentee in addition to any amounts the Rentee is required to pay to the Renter, which may include the fees attributable to those days that the Renter has been unable to lend the Items to other Rentees.\n\n8.2: Within a certain time frame after completing a Renting Transaction, Renters and Rentees can leave a public review (‘Review’) and submit a star rating (‘Rating’) about each other. Ratings or Reviews reflect the opinions of the individual User and do not reflect the opinions of Rentathon. Ratings and Reviews are not verified by Rentathon for accuracy and may be incorrect or misleading. Ratings and Reviews must be accurate and may not contain any offensive or defamatory language. Users are prohibited from manipulating the Ratings and Reviews system in any manner, such as instructing a third party to write a positive or negative Review about another User. Ratings and Reviews are part of a User's public profile with other relevant information such as number of Renting Transactions, number of cancellations, average response time and any other information Rentathon considers to be relevant.\n\n9.Fees and Payment\n\n8.1: Rentathon receives a commission from each of Renter and the Rentee for any and all Rental Transactions taking place through the Rentathon Platform (‘Rentathon Commission’). The Rentathon Commission will be twelve percent (12%) of the Loan Fee from each of the Renter and the Rentee. For Renters, Rentathon will retain twelve percent (12%) of the Loan Fee prior to its payment to Renter. For Rentees, Rentathon will charge the Rentee for the Loan Fee and the additional twelve percent (12%) of the Loan Fee upon Renter's acceptance of Rentee's request to enter into a Rental Transaction.\n\n8.2: You shall not engage in any practice which may avoid or lower the amount of Rentathon Commission that would otherwise have been payable had the Rental Transaction been completed using the Rentathon Platform (such practices collectively referred to as ‘Commission Avoidance’). Commission Avoidance includes, without limitation, entering into any Renting Transaction or otherwise coordinating to rent Items outside of the Rentathon Platform. In the event of engagement by any User(s) in any Commission Avoidance, such User(s) shall compensate Rentathon and waive and release Rentathon from any and all liabilities, claims, causes of actions, or damages as a result of the Rental Transaction as a result of such Commission Avoidance. In the event that you attempt to engage a User you met through the Rentathon Platform in a rental or transaction that does not use the Rentathon Platform, you are liable to pay a fine of up to the lesser of the Rentathon Commission or $200 as a penalty for doing so and Rentathon may terminate your account.\n\n8.3: We accept various payment methods for the Rentathon Platform, including, but not limited to, Mastercard, Visa, and American Express. For any fees on the Rentathon Platform payable to Rentathon or other Users, Rentathon or its third-party payment processor will bill your payment method submitted in connection with the Renting Transaction or otherwise provided with your account.\n\n8.4: Payments made through the Rentathon Platform are processed by Stripe. Payment processing services for Renters on Rentathon are provided by Stripe and are subject to the Stripe Connected Account Agreement, which includes the Stripe Terms of Service (collectively, the ‘Stripe Services Agreement’). By agreeing to these terms or continuing to operate as a Renter or Rentee on Rentathon, you agree to be bound by the Stripe Services Agreement, as the same may be modified by Stripe from time to time. As a condition of Rentathon enabling payment processing services through Stripe, you agree to provide Rentathon accurate and complete information about you and your business, and you authorize Rentathon to share it and any transaction information related to your use of the payment processing services provided by Stripe.\n\n10.Security\n\n10.1: Rentathon cares about the integrity and security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat our security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. You acknowledge that you provide your personal information at your own risk.\n\n11.Indemnity\n\n11.1: You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Rentathon and its subsidiaries, agents, licensors, managers, and other affiliated companies, and their employees, contractors, agents, officers and directors, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to the Rentathon Platform, including without limitation any data or content transmitted or received by you and your lending and/or borrowing of any Items; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms, including without limitation your breach of any of the representations and warranties above; (iii) your violation of any third-party right, including without limitation any right of privacy or Intellectual Property Rights; (iv) your violation of any applicable law, rule or regulation; (v) User Content or any content that is submitted via your account including without limitation misleading, false, or inaccurate information; (vi) your willful misconduct; or (vii) any other party's access and use of the Rentathon Platform with your unique username, password or other appropriate security code.\n\n12.Google Playstore\n\n12.1: The following applies to any Mobile Applications you acquire from the Google Play Store (‘Google-Sourced Software’): (i) you acknowledge that these Terms are between you and Rentathon only, and not with Google, Inc. (‘Google’); (ii) your use of Google-Sourced Software must comply with Google's then-current Google Play Store Terms of Service; (iii) Google is only a provider of the Google Play Store where you obtained the Google-Sourced Software; (iv) Rentathon, and not Google, is solely responsible for its Google-Sourced Software; (v) Google has no obligation or liability to you with respect to Google-Sourced Software or these Terms; and (vi) you acknowledge and agree that Google is a third-party beneficiary to these Terms as it relates to Rentathon's Google-Sourced Software.\n\n13.Contact\n\nPlease feel free to contact us at contact@rentathonapp.com with any questions regarding these Terms."
        android:fontFamily="@font/raleway"
        />

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>